<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Tech Hub</title>
    <link>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Tech Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Virtualization and Containers</title>
      <link>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/virtualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/virtualization/</guid>
      <description>Virtualization Nowadays everybody’s talking about (and using) containers for software integration and running apps on these isolated light-weight environments that turn out to be super convenient. Before even understanding what all this really is, it’s better to go back a bit to understanding what a virtual machine is, and even further, what virtualization is.
What is virtualization When somebody turns on a computer, this neat graphical interface shows up, with icons and buttons you can click on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate Facebook, so I created my own</title>
      <link>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/post_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/post_4/</guid>
      <description>Why build it Facebook is the most used social media.
 So many useless features   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best 5 tips from Elon Musk</title>
      <link>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/post_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/post_2/</guid>
      <description>1. You must feel compelled to do it - If you need inspiring words, don&amp;rsquo;t do it  What Elon is trying to say, is that we should be already motivated by the tasks we are going to do - In this case starting and managing a company.   In other words find things that inspire, or make them inspiring.
 2. Focus on improving product/service rather than spending time on BA/Finances  If a company spends more time on improving its products and/or services, its finances and business administration will easily come together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the coolest place for new ideas to emerge</title>
      <link>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>Everything in the universe is related to its complement. For example, a mobile application is related to electronics. You could easily deduce it since all software needs hardware on which it can run.
By &amp;ldquo;Complement&amp;rdquo; I mean anything other than the first subject. Therefore, we can say that a mobile application is related to something absolutely unimaginable like the sun. Even if it is for a single property. In case of the sun and the cell phone, they both use electromagnetic waves for different purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Networking in a nutshell</title>
      <link>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/post_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dfredude.github.io/my_blog/posts/post_1/</guid>
      <description>Why computer networking seems too complicated for everyone? I&amp;rsquo;ve seen that people tend to be afraid of getting into computer networking, specially when it comes to combining it with software.
The reason why computer networking is not understood by many, is because it&amp;rsquo;s kinda abstract since it&amp;rsquo;s grown to an enormous size which we can&amp;rsquo;t study in detail. Therefore we need to be imaginative by all these pieces of hardware and software that enable the entire internet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
